[
  {
    "question": "おはようございます",
    "answer": "Goodmorning",
    "language": "Japanese",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "こんばんは",
    "answer": "Goodevening",
    "language": "Japanese",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "ありがとう",
    "answer": "Thank you",
    "language": "Japanese",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "さよなら",
    "answer": "Good Bye",
    "language": "Japanese",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "いぬ",
    "answer": "Dog",
    "language": "Japanese",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "ねこ",
    "answer": "Cat",
    "language": "Japanese",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "おばさん",
    "answer": "Aunt",
    "language": "Japanese",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "おばあさん",
    "answer": "Grandmother",
    "language": "Japanese",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "おじさん",
    "answer": "Uncle",
    "language": "Japanese",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "おじいさん",
    "answer": "Grandfather",
    "language": "Japanese",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "おかあさん",
    "answer": "Mother",
    "language": "Japanese",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "おとうさん",
    "answer": "Dad",
    "language": "Japanese",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "おにいちゃん",
    "answer": "Big brother",
    "language": "Japanese",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "おねえちゃん",
    "answer": "Older sister",
    "language": "Japanese",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "いもうと",
    "answer": "Younger sister",
    "language": "Japanese",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "おとうと",
    "answer": "Younger brother",
    "language": "Japanese",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "今",
    "answer": "Now",
    "language": "Japanese",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "げつようび",
    "answer": "Monday",
    "language": "Japanese",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "привет",
    "answer": "hello",
    "language": "Russian",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "досвидания",
    "answer": "goodbye",
    "language": "Russian",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "как дела ?",
    "answer": "How are you ?",
    "language": "Russian",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "что делаешь",
    "answer": "What are you doing",
    "language": "Russian",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "хорошо",
    "answer": "Fine",
    "language": "Russian",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "плохо",
    "answer": "Badly",
    "language": "Russian",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "нормально",
    "answer": "mid",
    "language": "Russian",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "как",
    "answer": "how",
    "language": "Russian",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "это",
    "answer": "This",
    "language": "Russian",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "незнаю",
    "answer": "Don't know",
    "language": "Russian",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "знаю",
    "answer": "I know",
    "language": "Russian",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "иду",
    "answer": "I'm coming/going",
    "language": "Russian",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "туда",
    "answer": "there",
    "language": "Russian",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "question": "под",
    "answer": "under",
    "language": "Russian",
    "difficulty": "Medium"
  },
  {
    "question": "над",
    "answer": "over",
    "language": "Russian",
    "difficulty": "Medium"
  },
  {
    "question": "между",
    "answer": "between",
    "language": "Russian",
    "difficulty": "Medium"
  },
  {
    "question": "слева",
    "answer": "left",
    "language": "Russian",
    "difficulty": "Medium"
  },
  {
    "question": "справа",
    "answer": "right",
    "language": "Russian",
    "difficulty": "Medium"
  },
  {
    "question": "прямо",
    "answer": "directly",
    "language": "Russian",
    "difficulty": "Medium"
  },
  {
    "question": "зади",
    "answer": "behind",
    "language": "Russian",
    "difficulty": "Medium"
  }
]